

Lasse Lund-Egmose

Curriculum Vitae

Contact

☑ lasse@lle.engineer

+45 23 90 21 19

🏶 lle.engineer

in /Lasse-Lund-Egmose

Interests

- Engineering
- · Computer- and Cybersecurity
- · Ethical Hacking
- Cryptography
- · Operating Systems
- · Embedded Systems
- · Project Planning and Mgmt

Passion for technological engineering

Ever since I, at an early age, experienced the feeling of creating something that is comprehensible by a computer, I have known that I have a great interest in technology. Since then, I've worked hard to continuously broaden my skill set. I began my career with a focus on development of web solutions, but in recent years, I have shifted focus after finding a great interest in the areas of computer-and cybersecurity. Currently, I am studying towards a master's degree in Computer Science & Engineering, specializing in computer- and cybersecurity, at the Technical University of Denmark. In combination with my bachelor's degree in Software Technology, this will result in a Master of Science in Engineering degree (cand.polyt) in 2024.

Work experience

Student Assistant — Rambøll, Cyber and Information Security

Copenhagen, 2023-now

At Rambøll, I am currently a part of the Cyber and Information Security section — specifically the Governance, Risk, and Compliance department. My primary role is to support and assist in information security governance activities. I maintain and develop communication resources and training material, I ensure accuracy and upkeep of policies, procedures, and guidance documents, and I also handle other administrative tasks. This enables me to continuously enhance my knowledge and skills in the field of cyber and information security — especially from a cybersecurity administration/organizational perspective.

Teaching Assistant — Technical University of Denmark

Kongens Lyngby, 2022

For the course *Introduction to Software Technology*, I was hired to support the students' learning process during exercise sessions.

Backend Developer — Morningscore

Remote, 2019-2021

In this role, I developed parts of the Morningscore application. I worked on major projects, I had a great amount of responsibility, and I had to meet my deadlines — and did. I primarily dealt with integrations towards other systems such as the payment gateway (Stripe) and the CRM system (HubSpot).

Backend Developer / Project Manager — Morning Train

Odense C, 2018-2019

This was a full-time programming and project management job at a web agency, where I made websites and web solutions tailored to the needs of our customers. Apart from strengthening my development skills, I gained valuable experience in effectively assisting and communicating with clients, ensuring their needs were understood and met throughout the development process — resulting in successful outcomes. I also underwent a sales training program by *SalgsPiloterne*.



+45 23 90 21 19



Additional experience, Honors, and Certifications

Danish Cybersecurity Championship Team's preliminary roster

2023

I secured a spot on the Danish Cybersecurity Championship Team's preliminary roster ("Cyberlandsholdets bruttotrup") based on my performance in The Danish Cyber Championships (De Danske Cybermesterskaber). By demonstrating my skills within and passion for disciplines such as web exploitation, penetration testing, binary exploitation, reverse engineering, cryptography, forensics, and more, I achieved good results in the qualification round as well as in the regional final, and I secured an 8th place overall in the senior category of the national final.

Study abroad at University of Leeds

Leeds, 2021

Studying abroad at the University of Leeds was all about pushing my limits, embracing new challenges, and diving into English culture. The courses at University of Leeds allowed me to do just that, enriching my academic and personal qualifications. This experience shaped me into a more versatile engineer with a global perspective.

Microsoft SC-900: Security, Compliance, and Identity Fundamentals certification

2023

This certification validated my understanding of security, compliance, and identity concepts, as well as my knowledge of Microsoft Azure Active Directory, Microsoft Security solutions, and Microsoft compliance solutions.

The Academy for Talented Youth (Akademiet for Talentfulde Unge, ATU)

2016-2018

In high school, I participated in this challenging educational program for academically gifted students. I explored diverse subjects and collaborated with peers to strengthen my analytical and problem-solving skills driven by my passion for learning and personal growth.

Education

MSc. in Computer Science & Engineering – Technical University of Denmark Kongens Lyngby, 2022-now I am currently studying towards a master's degree in Computer Science & Engineering at the Technical University of Denmark. The courses I follow align with the Computer Security study line and include topics such as data security, system security, network security, cryptography, ethical hacking, forensics, etc. I expect to graduate in summer 2024, and, in combination with my bachelor's degree (BSc.) in Software Technology, I will receive a Master of Science in Engineering degree (cand.polyt).

BSc. in Software Technology – Technical University of Denmark GPA: 11.2 Kongens Lyngby, 2019-2022 I followed a wide variety of courses to learn the central aspects of software engineering. I also studied abroad at University of Leeds in the fall of 2021.

High school - Sct. Knuds Gymnasium GPA: 10.4

Odense M, 2015-2018

I followed the natural sciences study line. Furthermore, I was a member of The Academy for Talented Youth (ATU), and I was hired by Sct. Knuds Gymnasium to work as a tutor in my final year.



